

Alexandre Hervé Massoda Ma Mbeleck

5 Avenue Japoma Douala/ Cameroun

Phone: +33 648 536 457 (+237) 691 644 122

alexandrehervemassodamambeleck@g mail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandre-

Willingness to Relocate: Yes, with sponsorship.

Willingness to Travel: 100%

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

& SOFTWARES

BACKEND FRONT END SKILLS SKILLS MySQL WordPress PHP HTML5 REST API CSS3

Bootstrap **JavaScript** React JS.

SOFTWARES

VS Code XAMPP Development Tools Google Analytics MailChimp Hootsuite, Buffer

Feedly, Canvas Microsoft Office Git / GitHub

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Networks Architecting

Installation and administration of networks

IP Configuration

Systems installation (OS and Apps) Maintenance of systems (security

and configuration)

Provide Technical Solutions

Build products like Website and

Web apps

Unit Testing with Jasmine,

Quality Audit Web,

Technology survey

Best practices

SOFT SKILLS

Listening

Ability to learn and work alone or in a team

Proactive

Attention to details Love to Learn

Empathy

conflict resolution, **Excellent adaptability**

LANGUAGES

English: Fluent (C2). French: Native.

"I am a Frontend developer with a Bacc+4 from OpenClassrooms. As a developer I have nearly 2 years of experience in learning programming languages, innovations and best practices in software design. I have worked on real world JavaScript projects, including React JS in particular."

My GitHub profile: https://github.com/Xander1936

My HTML Portfolio: https://my-boostrap-portfolio.netlify.app/

Presentation Video Link: https://www.loom.com/share/64354b91f6364cc2a768f021702c0afb

EDUCATION

2021-2022: JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification at

FreeCodeCamp (in process).

September The Clever Programmer By Qazi: Learn React JS for free (finished) and The Ultimate JavaScript Course for 2022 to

Beginners (in process). now:

2020-2021: Bachelor Degree Diploma Level 6 of RNCP (Bac+4) in

Front-End developer path at OpenClassrooms. Paris, France

Certification on the principles of data networks and 2016-2017: certificates obtained in FTTH optical access networks

Paris, France module and in **Understanding 4G**.

Institut Mines-Télécom ParisTech (FUN-MOOC)

WORK EXPERIENCE

From January 2020 To August 2021

(Douala,

Cameroon)

EBENE MBA (ARTISTE-MUSICIENNE) **Independent Community Manager Consultant for EBENE** MBA (ARTIST-MUSICIAN).

- Creation of the official EBENE MBA Facebook page.
- Creation of the EBENE MBA YouTube account and channel.
- Publication and organic referencing of content (text, images and videos) on the official EBENE MBA Facebook Page.
- Setting up of a graphic and editorial charter.
- Publication and referencing of content on the EBENE MBA YouTube channel: single "MA CHOSE" audio:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DKV9VTUazLk and

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3fu2lbzV7UQ

From 10/03/2019 To 17/12/2020 (Douala, Cameroon)

Cameroon)

CIJ DOUALA3,

Volunteer support teacher and member of the web development jury on 15 January 2020 at the CIJDouala3-Littoral-Cameroon (Center for the Integration of Young People in the District of Douala3rd)

Missions:

- HTML5, CSS and WordPress courses and assessments
- Practical work and evaluations on HTML5, CSS and WordPress
- Best practices
- Correction of the end of training report
- Code review and testing of the Web interface
- Member of the jury for the Web Development course defence session

From October 2015 To January 2017 (Douala,

CYBERLINK DOUALA (IUT NDOGBONG and BONAPRISO), Technician / Sales Manager

Missions:

- Sale of internets tickets and bundles, call credit.
 - International Calls
 - Printing, Photocopying, scanning and typing
 - Operating Systems and Apps installation
 - Network Maintenance